《黑镜》
喂
Hello.
再说一遍
Just tell me whats happened.
什么?
And what is it?
我马上下来
I'll be right down.
怎么了?
What's happened?
苏珊娜
Er, Susannah.
苏珊娜?
Susannah?
苏珊娜公主
Princess Susannah.
她还好吧?
Is she all right?
还不确定
Dont know.
《国歌》
别杀我
Dont kill me.
不要杀我
Please dont kill me.
快念声明
Read the statement.
好
Yes. All right.
对着镜头?
On this screen?
没错
That is correct.
我是苏珊娜
I'm Susannah.
博蒙特女公爵
Duchess of Beaumont.
即众所周知的苏珊娜公主
Popularly known as Princess Susannah.
我现在身处之地...
I am in a place you...er...
以及幕后主谋都无迹可寻
cannot find, held by one you will not trace.
迈克尔·卡洛首相
Prime Minister Michael Callow...
迈克尔·卡洛首相  我的生命...
Prime Minister Michael Callow my life...
我的生命在您手中
my life depends on you.
如果今天下午四点
If you do not do precisely as instructed by, um...
您未能按照指示行事  我会...
by 4pm this afternoon, I will be...
我会被处决
I will be executed.
求求您
Please.
你在干嘛  继续播放
What are you doing? Keep it going.
首相  我认为目前有必要说明
Prime Minister, at this point, I think its important to say
我们已经完全肯定
that we are 100% certain
视频中确实是苏珊娜公主
that this is, indeed, Princess Susannah.
公主出席校友婚礼后
Her car was intercepted shortly after midnight,
半夜回家途中车辆被劫持
returning from the wedding of a college friend.
公主坚持要去参加
Shed insisted on going.
派保镖了吗?
But you had security on her?
两名贴身保镖  目前仍然昏迷
Two PPOs, still unconscious.
均被近身注射大量镇静剂
Heavy sedative, close range, each with a single puncture wound.
没有搏斗痕迹
No sign of struggle.
他们想要什么?
What do they want?
金钱?
Money?
释放圣战分子?
Release the Jihadi?
取消第三世界外债?
Scrap Third World debt?
还是他妈的拯救图书馆?
Save the fucking libraries?
我们已经证实了视频的真实性
We are convinced both the video and...
以及它的要求
the demand it contains are genuine.
什么要求?
What demand?
苏珊娜接下来所说的
What Susannah says next...
直接指向您个人
It concerns you directly, sir.
继续播放
Just play it.
只有一项要求  很简单
There is only one demand, and it is a simple one.
今天下午四点
At 4pm this afternoon,
迈克尔·卡洛首相
Prime Minister Michael Callow
要出现在英国电视的直播现场...
must appear on live British television...
所有网络  陆地和卫星电视
on all networks, terrestrial and satellite,
同时...  不...
and... No!
所有英国的网络  陆地和卫星电视
On all British networks, terrestrial and satellite,
要全程直播首相真刀真枪的和猪做爱
and have full unsimulated sexual intercourse with a pig.
你们想怎样
I dont understand!
视频余下部分是说明用什么技术进行直播
The video ends with a series of technical specifications for the broadcast.
你们为什么这么做?
Why are you doing this?
你们开玩笑  对吗
This is joke, right?
迈克尔  很有趣
"Ha ha, Mike! Ho ho."
是真的
It's real.
她说和猪
She said pig.
要和猪做爱
Sex with a pig.
他们想要我和猪做爱?
They want me to have sex with a pig?
现场直播
Live on television
今天下午
this afternoon.
可是  主谋是谁?
But what...? Who...?
我们在利用嵌入系统排列疑犯名单
Were checking with embedded operatives, compiling a list of suspects.
同时  既然开出了条件
Meanwhile, the demand has been made.
我们要尽快回应
Theres not long to formulate our response.
反正我不会和猪做爱
Well, I'm not fucking a pig!
第一条回应  此事不可能
Page one, thats not happening.
当然
Of course.
绝对肯定
Absolutely, sir.
能否与对方对话?
Well, have we established a dialogue with this...?
无法做到  没有任何电邮地址和密钥
We can't. Theres no e-mail address, no code word.
没有谈判途径
No channel for negotiation.
只能倾力救出苏珊娜
So we focus on finding Susannah. We get her back.
无论如何要摆平这事
However its done, I dont care. We stop this now.
每个人会全力以赴
Everyones working towards this.
等等  此事要保密  不要泄露出去
Yes. No. Not everyone. A dedicated core team. This can't go wide.
把这件事和谐掉  不要让传媒得悉
Keep it so far from the press its on the other side of Jupiter.
就我们知道就行
This only exists in this room.
恐怕太迟了
It's already outside it.
如果有骇客胆敢勘查这事  让他们消失
If there are hacks sniffing around, shut them down.
绝对杀无赦  斩立决
Super fucking Godzilla injunction with ten-inch Whitehall fangs!
这段视频源自YouTube
This video came from YouTube.
什么?
What?
一小时前由加密IP上传
It was uploaded via an encrypted IP an hour ago.
快删掉
Well, get it off there!
九分钟后就删了  但已无法阻止它流传出去
We did after nine minutes, long enough for it to be duplicated and spread.
流传?  有多少人看了这视频?
Spread? How many people have seen this?
我们删掉一个  就有六个在其它地方出现
We take down one, six clones pop up elsewhere.
多少人看过?
How many people?
目前估计有五万人
50,000. Thats our current estimate.
新闻媒体早拿到视频
The news rooms have got it.
播放了吗?
Theyre running this on air?
没有  我们发布了五级国防机密通知
No. We put a type five D notice out and theyre complying.
目前为止  它成了微博的热门话题
For now. It's trending on Twitter.
该死的互联网
Oh! For... Fucking internet!
怎么办  有没有先例可供参考?
What now? What's the play book?
史无前例  首相
This is virgin territory, Prime Minister.
无前车可鉴
Theres no play book.
[第一部分完]
[第二部分]
苏珊娜公主被绑架了
Princess Susannahs been kidnapped!
吓死我了
You scared the shit out of me!
Youtube上有了
There's on Youtube.
快去工作
Go to work!
真刀真枪的和猪做爱
And have full unsimulated sexual intercourse with a pig.
不可能  肯定是恶作剧
No way. It's a piss take, man. Look at it!
你们想怎样
I dont understand!
为什么新闻上没有
Why isn't it on the news?
卡尔顿·布鲁姆颇具争议的展览会
Carlton Blooms controversial exhibition
较原计划提前三周结束了
closes three weeks ahead of schedule...
怎么描述呢  不雅行为?
How do we describe it? "An indecent act"?
大家都看过视频  都知道细节
Everyones seen the video. They know the details.
如果我们提及兽交  电信监管机构绝对会动怒
If we mention bestiality Ofcom would be pissed off.
该死的电信监管
Fuck Ofcom!
我们要遵守国防机密通知
Were observing the D Notice.
肯定要做点事情
Surely were going to do something.
遵守国防机密通知
The honorning D Notice!
那是自愿遵守的
The voluntary D Notice!
运动员职业道德还不是靠自觉
It may be a sportsman-like gesture but we are making it.
这事性命攸关  我们照章办事
A womans life is at stake! We follow procedue.
我时间表上排满了  所有观众都在问...
My timeline consists 100% of viewers asking...
为何电视台不播放  怎么回答?
why were not covering it. How do I reply?
别回答
You dont.
这太保守了
Yeah, that's totally backwords!
不能播出
No one else has broken record.
BBC  天空电视台 都没有
Not the Beeb, not Sky. That is totally backwards.
Facebook的覆盖则非常全面
Facebooks coverage is pretty comprehensive!
也许吧
Yes, that's maybe.
就像911发生时  我们在教大家做三明治
It's like 9/11s happening and we broadcasting sandwich recipe
这里不是聊天室
Were not a chat room!
美国有线电视新闻网和福克斯广播公司跟进了
It's on CNN and Fox.
还有微软全国广播公司  半岛电视台  日本放送协会...
And MSNBC, Al Jazeera, NHK...
好了
All right!
这是什么星球
Oh, God! This planet!
莎拉  你负责绑架部分
OK, Sarah, cover the snatch itself.
达蒙负责群众反应  美兰负责皇室态度
Damon, public reaction. Meera, the royal angle, upcoming marriage, etc.
西蒙  你来定好基调
Simon, set tone with Standards.
我们需要报道  但别让观众把早饭喷了
We need to explain this without viewers sicking up their Weetabix.
肯负责网络反响  新范例  微博  阿拉伯之春等
Ken, the internet, new paradigm, Twitter, Arab spring, all that.
丹  图片要经我许可
Dan, all graphics run past me.
实用点  别用粉红猪小妹
Functional... no Peppa Pigs.
马莱卡  准备一下公主的讣告
Malaika, update the princess obit VT.
讣告?
The Obit VT?
首先  我无可避免要告知汤姆一声
Mm-hm. First, an awkward phone call. Least I can do is warn Tom.
我们要遵守国防机密通知
We put a D Notice on it.
汤姆  全世界都在广播
It's gone global, Tom.
别播  我求你
Dont. I'm begging you.
别播放  马丁
Dont run it, Martin.
对不起  我帮不了你
Look, I'm sorry. I can't help you.
你知道你会给我捅多大娄子吗
You know how much help youre getting hereon in?
满口胡言的UKN就是狗屁
Multiply nothing by shit-all! UKN are dead for us!
等着爆菊吧...
Shove it up your arse you fucking...
- 很有雅兴  - 是男的
- Interesting. -  A man.
- 男的?  - 男的
- Man? -  A man!
汤姆  既然你参加了
Tom, so youre across it...
我在拟定紧急计划
I'm exploring contingency plans.
我已告诉过卡莱特
I briefed Callett.
卡莱特  这是来自蓝眼公司的尼尔
Mr Callett. Noel, from Blue Eye.
他给HBO的什么月球剧做的特效得了艾美奖
Noel won an Emmy by his effects work on that HBO moon Western thing.
宁静海
Sea Of Tranquillity.
业内佼佼者
You wont find better.
你能否将头部图像移植到另一个人?
Can you map a head onto a body live?
这要看镜头的稳定系数
Depends if your cameras moving.
绑匪要求要单手持DV并走动拍摄
Rule sheet specifies a single hand-held camera in a constant roving motion.
色情电影风格  他很懂行  作假很难
Yeah, Gonzo style. He knows his shit. Thats tough.
实况直播?
"Fruition to be transmitted in full"?
重点是画面  给直播的表演者换脸
Focus on the visuals. Different face mapped onto a live performer.
可能性很小
Fringes of possibility...
期限是四点钟  两点以前给我们答复
Deadlines at four. We need to know if its workable by two.
做不到
Cant happen.
不行也得行
It has to.
排除基地组织和爱尔兰共和军
Our embeds have ruled out the major players. It's not AQ, not IRA.
剩下就是激进分子和愤青
This is whats left... radicals, hate groups.
和曾威胁过您或皇室的人员
People whove threatened yourself or the royals.
正逐个传唤他们
Theyre being pulled in as we speak.
最好多问点问题
For more than questioning, I hope.
肯定有人知道点什么
Somebody know something.
新闻还是没报么?
Is it still not on the telly?
没有  肯定是恶作剧
Nothing. Must be a hoax.
或者是新闻封锁
Or a black-out.
来了
Oh! Heads up!
以下是UKN突发新闻
Some major breaking news here on UKN.
就在刚才  已证实
In the last minutes, it's been confirmed
博蒙特女公爵苏珊娜遭到绑架
that Susannah, Duchess of Beaumont has been kidnapped.
一段匿名上传的网络视频显示
A video uploaded anonymously to the Internet
苏珊娜公主不断求饶
appears to depict the princess pleading for her life.
视频提出一项离奇赎回条件
The video also contains a bizarre ransom demand of a personal nature
矛头直指首相
involving the Prime Minister,
并附加直播技术要求
this is followed by detailed list of instructions relating to the enactment of this demand.
警方正在全国搜集可疑分子情报
As police round up potential suspects...
片中出现布拉德福警方的突袭行动
this viewer video shows officers raiding an address in Bradford.
一名宗教压力团体相关人士正被拖向货车
A man thought to be connected with a religious pressure group, dragged to a waiting van...
若绑匪是恐怖分子  公主早就身首异处了
If its terrorists, theyll take her head off.
- 闭上臭嘴  - 说说而已
- For fucks sake, man! -  Just saying.
对方大概会要求一百万赎金
They'll be asking for a million quid or something.
他们是要首相和猪做爱
They want him to do it with a pig.
每日电讯报已放出整片并开设互动讨论区
Telegraph has the whole video and an interactive timeline. Tonally stark.
报道风格严谨  含蓄地将条件称为性行为
Brief mention of the ransom being "a sex act".
并不露骨
Nothing too gross.
太阳报用劫持和公主的特写做头版
Sun runs with "Taken". Big grab of Susannah...
我当然想和你喝一杯
Of course I still want that drink.
那给我点内部消息
Then give me something.
不可能
That wont be possible.
事后我不会亏待你的
I'm friendly when I drink. Very friendly when I'm grateful.
无可奉告
There's no comment at this time.
卫报弄了个直播博客
The Guardian are running a fucking live blog
附上了关于猪象征意义历史的短文
and a short piece on the historical symbolism of the pig.
还有五个小时
only five hours away,
UKN达蒙·布朗分析公众的反应
UKNs Damon Brown analyses the public reaction to the crisis.
不同寻常的一天
It's the day like no other.
绑架视频已有超过一千八百万人数浏览
The kidnap video has been watched by over 18 million people.
社交网站估计每分钟会出现一万条微博
Social networking sites are a... buzz with 10,000 Tweets per minute.
在我们等待唐宁街回应此事的同时
So, while we wait for Downing Street to respond,
毫无疑问全国民众亦纷纷表态
the nation is voicing its opinion.
我不赞成向威胁妥协而做出侮辱人格的事
I dont think anyone should concede to any humiliation under threat.
我无法容忍观看此事
I couldnt bear to watch that.
我不会看  想着就觉得可怕
I wont be tuning in. Just thinking about it is horrible.
恶心  想想就恶心
That's disgusting. It is disgusting. Think about it.
是恶心  但事后首相会成为英雄
It is disgusting but...  after that, hes gonna be hero.
公众会认为他疯了  赶他下台
People will look at him like hes insane and take his position away.
在电视上看到会非常滑稽
It will be hilarious to see that on TV.
对议员来说  这并不是多变态的事
Nothing too abnormal for MPs.
众议员和首相都爱胡搞瞎搞
Theyre all sexual deviants, all MPs and Prime Ministers.
严刑逼供  也没有线索
Weve been squeezing hard, but nothing concrete.
这是我家  你怎能...
It's my house! You can't...
你站在我家走廊上  握着我家的门把手
You're in my doorway. You're touching my door handle!
我们可以聊聊吗?
Could I have a word?
- 不会到那一步的  - 如果警方找不到公主?
- It wont come to that. -  And if they dont find her?
军情五处已经找到一个名字
MI5 have got a name.
- 他们正在包围那里  - 哪里?
- Theyre surrounding the place now. -  Where?
- 什么?  - 是哪里?
- What? -  Wheres the place?
- 特鲁罗  - 为什么说谎
- Truro. -  Why are you lying?
- 我?  - 你在撒谎
- What? -  Youre lying!
特鲁罗?  骗鬼
Truro? Jesus!
我只是不想你担心
I dont want you worrying.
你从来都不会宠我  现在也不用
Youve never patronised me. Dont start now.
不管怎样  简直匪夷所思
Whoever this is, is insane.
- 然而公主被挟持  - 会有办法的
- And has a princess. -  Well get through this.
不是别的公主  是这位公主
Not any princess... the princess.
热衷Facebook和环保  集万民宠爱的公主
Princess bloody Facebook, bloody eco-conscious national sweetheart.
反正我不会做那事
I wont have to do anything.
- 所有人等着笑话我们  - 别瞎说
- Everyones laughing at us. -  You dont know that.
人性本恶
I know people.
喜欢羞辱别人  喜欢幸灾乐祸
We love humiliation. We can not laugh.
不会发生那种事的
Nothing is going to happen.
公众早就幻想那事了
It's already happening in their heads.
他们正幻想我老公在和猪做爱
In their heads, thats what youre doing, what my husband is doing.
这实在是...
'Cause it's just...
- 别让这种事发生  - 简
- Please! -  Jane.
怎么了?
What?
皇室打来电话
Palace on the phone, sir.
让亚历克斯拖延他们
Get Alex to stall them.
她早和跟她聊了十分钟
Shes already been speaking to her for ten minutes.
她?
"Her"?
是女王来电
It's the Queen herself.
接吧
Go on.
最后期限四点将至  全世界屏住呼吸
As the 4pm deadline draws nearer, the world holds its breath...
他们会找头母猪来?
Would they use a female pig?
要求是那样
It's on the list.
还指定拍摄角度和场设
List of rules, specifies camera angles and things.
- 就像电影道格玛95  - 根本不像
- Like dogme 95. -  It's not like Dogme 95.
- 道格玛95是什么?   - 电影运动
- What's Dogme 95? -  Cinematic movement.
拉斯·冯·提尔
Lars von Trier.
规定导演不用配乐
That's the rules for a director... no background music,
不打光  保证真实性
only natural light and so on, for authenticity.
同理  这次也不能造假
Same as these, so they can't cheat,
只能来真的
it cut another guys arse pumping away.
简直史无前例
I mean I can't think of anything remotely like this.
新形式的恐怖主义
Entirley new form of terrorism...
- 我是这么看  - 不是伊斯兰教主义者
- Thats the point!  - It's not Islamist nature.
- 用猪跟他们的教义相抵触  - 这就是关键!
- To request a pig is specifically abhorrent. - That's exactly the point!
跟猪做爱
To make love to a pig!
做爱?
Make love?
岔开话题  不要讨论细节
Steer them away from the grisly details.
我们就不讨论任何细节
Lets not dwell on any of the details.
此事已成为全国热门话题
This is already a huge national talking point.
不正中幕后黑手的下怀?
Isnt this precisely what whoever is behind this is looking for?
女王陛下怎么说?
Hows Her Majesty taking it?
"我相信你会不惜一切救回公主"
"I trust youll do everything in your power to get her back."
- 女王的原话  - 我们是要不惜一切
- That's what she said. -  And we are.
不是"你们"  是"你"  她单指我
It wasnt a collective "you". It was a singular "you", ie me.
有新进展
Sir, we may have something.
杰米追踪到视频出处
Jamies been tracing the videos origin.
不是说无法追踪
I thought it was untraceable.
技术上是不行
Technically yes.
但我想我们可以分析已知的
But, so I thought, "Work with what we do know".
视频在上传前是57.3兆
And that video, before Youtube compression it was 57.3 meg.
是算法
Algorithm.
总之  我们得知该片于凌晨三点十六分上传
Anyway, we also know it was uploaded at 3.16am.
用回溯查看全国在当时
So I ran a nationwide traceback on uninterrupted one-way uploads
不间断上传了57.3兆的用户
of precisely 57.3 meg in the minutes leading up to 3:16,
范围缩小到了一个邮编
and the closest I can get is a postcode.
这里的某个地方
It came from somewhere in there.
- 好像一个校园  - 对  但2010年关闭了
- Looks like a campus. -  Yeah. Closed 2010.
一直废弃
It's been empty since.
该区域最新卫星地图如何?
Latest i-sat image on this area?
昨晚凌晨三点捕捉的图像
3am flyover shot from last night...
好像有灯光
Looks like it had lights on.
找到他了  找到他了
We got him. We got him.
通知当局  全体出击  我负责指挥
Alert the local team. Full squad. I'll man it.
戴上摄像头盔  方便监视行动
With helmet-cam relay. We can watch the operation.
准备新闻发布会  汤姆
Press office, OK, Tom?
妥妥的
Yes!
[第二部分完]
[第三部分]
有信心吗?
Right. Confident?
有点纠结  处理下就行了
It's a kick-bollock scramble, but with finessing it should be OK.
最好快点  演员快来了
Finesse quickly. Our performers on his way.
从未遇到这种情况  通常我不会答应
It's a new one for me, obviously. I wouldnt normally... You know.
- 有看过我的电影吗?  - 没有
- You seen any of my films? -  No.
我为人相当传统  扑倒办事  提裤走人
I'm pretty trad... bish, bash, bosh. In, out.
我在想  发票上怎么写呢?
What do I put on the invoice? Thats what I'm wondering.
不会有发票
There wont be any invoicing.
要着手两份行动声明
Need to prep two statements explain rescue operation.
成功失败各一份
Good outcome. Bad outcome.
营救行动?
Rescue operation?
特警队正赶往位于白金汉郡
Goon squads heading for postcode in Buckinghamshire.
邮编HP8-4TD  大学校园之类的
HP8-4TD, a college or something.
估计他们到了
They should be there by now.
嗯  我已经降低了亮度
Yeah, I've reduced the luminance...
卡莱特探员  这位是弗林先生
Agent Callett, this is Mr Flynn.
或者叫我无觉神棒  艺名
AKA, Rod Senseless. Stage name.
那好吧
Yeah. Well...
你得把这穿上
You need to get into this.
这附近有更衣室吗?
Is there a dressing room I can use?
没有
No.
女演员呢?
Wheres my co-star?
事前不亲她一下是很粗鲁的
Be rude not to give her a kiss beforehand.
在外面的卡车上呢
Outside in the truck.
原来他挺阳光的  不是吗?
Full of joie de vivre, isn't he?
你得把这东西套头上
You also need to wear this... on your head.
门板给撬开了  他们就是从那进去的
Boards been prised away. Thats where they got in.
目标确定
Target identified.
谢谢  长官
Commissioner. Thank you.
发现疑似入口  有何指示?
So, team red... Any orders, boss?
继续侦查  等待命令
Continue reconnaissance and await instructions before you proceed.
离截止时间下午四点还有三个小时
With the 4pm deadline three hours away,
留给首相的时间不多了...
time is running out for the Prime Minister...
他们突进去了?
They got in, yeah?
要是突进去了我还在这?
Do you think Id be here if they had?
我们准备了两份声明
We've got statements for either outcome.
听着  新闻报道充满同情
Listen, coverage is very sympathetic.
现在不是讨论新闻的时候
Cant think about coverage now!
舆论在我们这边?
But its on-side?
公众都充满同情
Strong undercurrent of sympathy.
所有民调显示公众对劫匪的憎恶
Every poll indicates understanding,
以及对事件的愤怒  但没有针对你
disgust with the captor, outrage at the whole thing, but not at you.
万一沃克的小队失败了  我是说万一
If Walkers team fuck up, I'm not saying they will, but if they do,
群众趋向于不妥协
the public anticipates non-compliance.
会出现一些异议
Therell be squawks from the usuals,
但这不是主流民意
but it's not "England expects".
如果她被害  不会影响到你  这是底线
If he kills her, theres no blood on your hands. Bottom line.
只有几小时了  营救时间不多了
With hours to go, time is running out for the security services.
在我身边的是莉迪亚...
Joining us is actress Lydia...
还以为来自IB7呢
Thought this was coming from IB7.
我们掐掉了  直接播
We trimmed the edges so its coming direct.
那波霸哪里来的?
Twinkle tits from?
演唐顿庄园的  和公主认识
Actress, Downton Abbey, knows the princess.
你的包裹  有人留在接待处的
This came for you, left at reception.
快递送来的
Courier dropped it off.
知道这玩意儿怎么用吗
Know how to plug this in?
杰克  打电话给警察  把这拿走
Jack, call the police. Take it!
找人把这事报道一下先
Get someone to shoot that first.
这他妈到底是什么?
What the fuck is this?
(我说过规则  禁止作弊)
(无觉神棒?  得了吧!)
现在插播一条突发新闻
Some more breaking news,
疑似苏珊娜公主的一截断指
and a severed finger, thought to belong to Princess Susannah,
连同一段视频被寄给了UKN总部
has been delivered to UKN, along with a video
显然是绑架者从公主手上切下来的
apparently showing the kidnapper removing it from the princess.
UKN已将所有证物移交苏格兰场...
UKN News has passed all material to Scotland Yard...
见鬼
Fucking hell!
我都不敢看了  首相得照他们说的做
Oh, God! I can't watch this! Hes got to do what they want.
对  他没得选
Yes, he fucking has!
视频中的声明
Which contained a statement
指责唐宁街破坏了游戏规则
accusing Downing Street of attempting to break the rules
目前情形堪忧  四点期限快到了
This grim development comes just
天啊
Jesus!
我弄错了吗  但我们的绑匪
Unless I'm mistaken, our mystery man specified
一开始就说不允许在视频上动手脚  对吗
no visual trickery in his original demand, didn't he?
- 我认为这是必要的...  - 必要
- I considered it necessary... -  considered it necessary.
- 建议你...  - 去他的
- To divise... -  FUCKING HELL!
- 迈克...  - 闭嘴
- Mike...! -  Dont!
这既不是...
It's nor...
你再敢多说  我发誓我一定会...
One word, I swear I will fucking...!
你做了什么?  亚历克斯
What did you do, Alex?
我有个备用计划
I had a back-up plan.
找个人干这事
A man prepared to do it,
然后找个特技公司把他的头像换成你的
and an FX company that would paint your head onto his shoulders.
你真觉得这方法可行?
You actually thought that would work?
我认为值得一试
I believed it worth considering.
这么想你就太傻了
Then youre a stupid bitch.
我是真心为你考虑
With your interest at heart.
还有谁知道这计划
Who knew about this?
很少  不过片场的几个痞子似乎
A select few. It seems some idiot at the studio
认出了我们原先准备替代你的人选
recognised our designated performer,
把他的照片发到微博  结果被人肉出来了
Tweeted a photo and the online hivemind did the maths.
情况不是很理想
It's not playing well.
谁的情况
With who?
都不理想
With, er...anyone.
几小时前  公众舆论站在首相一边
A few hours ago, public opinion was behind Prime Minister Callow,
只有百分之二十八的人认为
with only 28% of the public believing
他应该满足绑匪古怪的非法要求
he should fulfil the bizarre and illegal request.
但这段视频的公布
In the wake of these images,
公主的断指使民众情绪迅速发生转变
and the delivery of the princesss finger, the mood is shifting.
这很丢人  但无法和公主遭受的折磨相比
It'll be humiliating, but nothing compared to her suffering.
断指都出现了  他只能让步
With the appearance of finger. He has just got to do it.
他必须做  还有别的选择么?
Yes, he has to do it. What's the alternative?
我们可以换个首相  但不能失去公主
We can get another Prime Minister. We can't live without a princess.
他当然必须做
Of course he has to do it.
要是救不出公主  他也得玩完
If he doesn't get her released, hes finished, isn't he?
网络民调显示  有百分之八十六的网民
Online polls suggest that 86% of voters
现在认为首相应该满足绑匪的要求
now believe the demand should be met.
达蒙·布朗
Damon Brown...
沃克小队什么时候开始突击?
When are Walkers team hitting the college?
- 他们需要时间...  - 别再废话了
- They need time... -  No more pissing around.
- 朱利安不怎么赞成...  - 我赞成
- Julians advising against... -  I'm advising for.
让他们现在就行动
They go in now.
马上
我要的讣告在哪?
Wheres my obit VT?
你相信我现在就在公主被囚禁的地方吗
What would you say if I said I was near where Susannahs being held?
信你才怪
I'd say bullshit.
你错了
Then you'd be wrong.
- 你有搭档吗?   - 我又不傻
- Have you got a crew with you? -  I'm not stupid.
马莱卡?
Malaika?
能看到吗?
Are you getting this?
能  听着  注意安全
Yeah. Dont put yourself in any danger.
能看到吗?
Still getting this?
是的  马莱卡  注意安全
Yeah. Just stay safe, Malaika. Be careful!
如果行动失败...
If this doesn't work...
我们就得...
we need...
特警  趴下  全都趴下
Armed police! Lay down on the floor! Lay down on the floor!
前进
Move!
操
Fuck!
是个圈套
It's a decoy.
他们一定是通过代理服务器上传的
They must have bounced the upload from here with a proxy.
发送者可能在任何地方  抱歉
They could be anywhere. I'm sorry.
天啊
Jesus!
他们在看着她呢
They're looking right at her!
他们看不到她的  有道玻璃
They can't see her. There's a screen here.
马莱卡  确保他们无法...
Malaika, make sure they can't...
趴下  不许动
Stay down! Dont move!
快跑  马莱卡  快
Run, Malaika! Run!
快从那出去  快
Get out of there. Come on!
特警
Armed police!
是他吗?
Is it him?
- 老天!  - 杰克  杰克他妈的在哪?
- Jesus! -  Jack! Where the fuck is Jack?
冲  冲
Advance! Advance! Advance!
趴下
Get down!
是UKN的  好像是马莱卡  她是UKN的
UKN. It's Malaika something or other. Shes from UKN.
- 你是记者吗?  - 是的
- You press? -  Yes.
去你妈的皇家电视学会奖
There goes your RTS Award.
那儿一定还有些什么
There must be something.
- 那里什么都没有  迈克  - 起码有个线索吧
- Theres nothing there, Mike. -  There'll be a clue. Some evidence.
- 我们已经尽最大努力了  - 就他妈解救了人体模型
- Weve done all we can. -  You rescued mannequin.
- 我很抱歉  迈克尔...  - 去你的  朱利安
- I'm sorry, Michael... -  Fuck off, Julian!
已经三点二十了  我们没时间了
Michael. It's 20 past three. Were out of time.
我们还有时间
Were not out of time!
还有时间
Were not out of time.
这不可能
It's not going to happen.
- 对民众来说...  - 去他的民众
- To the public... -  Fuck the public!
对于民众来说  你会饱受质疑
To the public, this would be one man of questionable popularity
将个人得失置于一个女孩的生命之上
putting personal embarrassment over the life of a girl.
他不会放过她  她可能早就死了
They will not release her anyway. She's probably already dead.
如果她没死  他会把她杀了并上传视频
If she isn't, hell kill her and upload the video.
所有人都会见证  全世界都会见证
Everyone will see it. The world will see it.
到时群情激奋  你就垮台了
The mood will border on insurrection and you will be destroyed,
我敢向您保证...  彻底垮台
I guarantee you... utterly destroyed.
民调显示了同样的结果
The polling bears that out.
您不仅成为丢脸的政治家  还会遗臭万年
You wont just be a disgraced politician, you'll be despised individual.
公众  皇室包括我党都赞成妥协
The public, the Palace and the Party insist on compliance.
去他娘的我党
Fuck the Party!
如果您拒绝  据我所知
Refuse, and I've been advised...
您的人身安全将无法得到保障
that we cannot guarantee your physical safety.
甚至牵连您的家人
Or that of your family.
针对转播我已经做了相关部署
I've made arrangements for the broadcast.
我不能...
I can't...
我很遗憾  迈克尔  可我们无能为力
I'm sorry, Michael. It's out of your hands.
[第三部分完]
[第四部分]
我们正为您现场直播
Let's take you live to the scene in central London.
我们看到  首相的专车正穿越伦敦
as we see the Prime Ministers car travelling across London...
- 看来他要妥协了  - 这世界太疯狂  还是回火星吧
- Hes got to do it. -  The world's bloody broken.
显然是驱车向西前往班克赛德演播室
Appears to be heading west to Bankside Studios.
我们已经颁布法令...  从明天凌晨开始
Weve ratified the law... after midnight,
储存任何相关图像和视频的行为都被视为非法
it'll be a criminal offence to store any recording or images of the event.
他们已经告诫民众请勿观看
Theyre doing an announcement to warn people off even watching,
会播放蜂鸣声来使民众感到恶心
some sonic tone that causes nausea.
当公众意见
When public opinion has very much hardened,
在邮寄断指事件后如此强硬时
following the delivery of the princesss severed finger.
随着下午四点的临近
As the 4pm deadline approaches,
整个国家万人空巷
the nation is at a standstill
关注这一重大事件的发展走向
watching the extraordinary situation play out.
不得不说  这一事件已经引起全球关注
Just to remind you, this is now a story of global significance...
迈克尔·卡洛展现了非凡的勇气
"Michael Callow has displayed incredible bravery"
这事关生死
"in what was a matter of life or death."
这是开场白  接着...
Thats how it opens, then we should move on...
那好吧
OK. Yeah.
准备就绪了吗?
Everything prepared?
是的  女士
Yes, maam.
下药了吗?
It's sedated?
已经注射过了  很温顺
Injection. It's docile.
该进去了
It's time to go in now.
前所未有的事件
An unprecedented nature.
这是一份官方声明
This is an official announcement.
首相将会做出一些不雅的行为
The Prime Minister will perform an indecent act on your screens.
以期确保公主的安全释放
in the hope that it will ensure the release of Princess Susannah.
任何录影和储存将被视为非法
Recording or possessing a copy of this broadcast will become illegal.
建议所有观众立即关闭电视
All viewers are advised to turn off their televisions immediately.
在以下蜂鸣后正式开始播放
The broadcast will commence after the following tone.
为遵守规则  您必须不停的...
We're complying with the stipulated rules. So you have to keep going...
您必须坚持到最后
youll have to see it through to the end.
视线等高处会播放性爱视频
Weve placed visual aids in your eyeline, which might help if you...
以防您有某些麻烦
get into trouble.
心理学家建议
The suggestion were getting from psychologists
你尽可能把时间放长一些
is that you should take as long as you need.
如果您表现匆促  会被误解为饥渴
If you rush, it might be misinterpreted as eagerness
甚至愉悦
or even enjoyment.
里面只有一个摄像团队
It's just a skeleton crew inside.
环境完全封闭
Closed set.
他出现啦
There he is!
我希望此举能换回苏珊娜公主的安全
I trust this will bring about the safe return of Princess Susannah.
我...
I...
我爱我的妻子
I love my wife.
愿上帝宽恕我
May God forgive me.
天哪  这家伙太惨了
Jesus! Poor bastard!
都快一个小时了
But its been on for nearly an hour.
我们在见证历史
It's history, this.
我们找到苏珊娜了
Weve got her. Susannah.
他们把她放了?
They released her?
她在城里乱撞呢  被下了药
Stumbling about in the city. Sedated.
什么都不记得  但毫发无伤
She can't remember anything, but she's unharmed.
但她的手指?
But her finger?
不是她的  DNA显示是男性手指
Not hers. DNA shows its male.
什么?
What?
还有  监控录像在三点半拍到了她
There is one other thing. There's a CCTV grab of her from half three.
她在离四点还有半小时就被释放了
It seems he let her go 30 minutes before it happened.
为什么?
Why?
我想他料到大家都会在室内看电视
My guess... he knew everyone would be elsewhere watching screens.
也就是说这是一份宣言
So its a statement.
这事到此为止了
That's what this was all about, making a point.
我们要不要...?
Should we, er...?
报告中不要把这事写进去
Lose that page of the report.
确保没人知道这事  尤其是首相本人
No-one sees it, especially the PM.
我知道了
Of course.
好消息  迈克尔
Good news, Michael.
您救了她  她还活着  安然无恙
You saved her. Susannahs alive and well.
在遭受羞辱一周年当天
On the one-year anniversary of his humiliating ordeal,
迈克尔·卡洛很自信  显然没有受到影响
an apparently unconcerned Michael Callow put in an assured performance
在妻子简的陪同下与公众会面
at a public appearance, accompanied by his wife Jane.
该事件其他中心人物也接受了采访
The other central figure in events was also before the camera
在昨晚的英勇儿童颁奖会
at last nights Children Of Valour Awards.
苏珊娜公主在宣布怀孕后
Princess Susannah made her first public appearance
首度出现在公共场合
since announcing her pregnancy.
一年前  特纳奖得主
It was one year ago that the Turner Prize-winning artist,
艺术家卡尔顿·布鲁姆
Carlton Bloom,
迫使首相做出不雅之举
coerced the Prime Minister into committing an indecent act.
随着一周年的到来  一则艺术评论引发了争议
As the anniversary arrived, one art critic caused controversy
该评论称其为本世纪首部伟大作品
by describing it as "the first great artwork of the 21st century".
然而文化学者则持相反的观点
While cultural commentators debate its significance,
毋庸置疑  全球十三亿的收视率
with a global audience of 1.3 billion,
这是个全民参与的事件
it was an event in which we all participated.
但这次事件并未击垮首相
The incident failed to destroy a Prime Minister,
他的支持率同比高出了三个百分点
who holds an approval rating three points higher than last year.
达蒙·布朗  UKN
Damon Brown, UKN.
简
Jane.
简  求你了
Jane, please.